export const questionL4 = [
    {
      question: '9 / 1',
      choices: ['2', '8', '1', '9'],
      correctAnswer: '9',
    },
    {
      question: '6 / 3',
      choices: ['12', '13', '6', '2'],
      correctAnswer: '2',
    },
    {
      question: '8 / 4',
      choices: ['2', '18', '4', '12'],
      correctAnswer: '2',
    },
    {
      question: '24 / 6',
      choices: ['21', '4', '12', '24'],
      correctAnswer: '4',
    },
    {
      question: '8 / 2',
      choices: ['26', '20', '15', '4'],
      correctAnswer: '4',
    },
    {
      question: '12 / 4',
      choices: ['36', '3', '18', '6'],
      correctAnswer: '3',
    },
    {
      question: '28 / 4',
      choices: ['7', '14', '8', '2'],
      correctAnswer: '7',
    },
    {
      question: '9 / 3',
      choices: ['2', '4', '6', '3'],
      correctAnswer: '3',
    },
    {
      question: '3 / 3',
      choices: ['2', '3', '0', '1'],
      correctAnswer: '1',
    },
    {
      question: '24 / 4',
      choices: ['9', '7', '1', '6'],
      correctAnswer: '6',
    },
    {
        question: '20 / 5',
        choices: ['3', '4', '10', '6'],
        correctAnswer: '4',
      },
      {
        question: '21 / 7',
        choices: ['8', '3', '6', '5'],
        correctAnswer: '3',
      },
      {
        question: '18 / 2',
        choices: ['7', '9', '4', '10'],
        correctAnswer: '9',
      },
      {
        question: '36 / 9',
        choices: ['8', '11', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '4',
      },
      {
        question: '14 / 2',
        choices: ['2', '6', '8', '7'],
        correctAnswer: '7',
      },
      {
        question: '36 / 6',
        choices: ['7', '6', '9', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '6',
      },
      {
        question: '63 / 7',
        choices: ['12', '8', '5', '9'],
        correctAnswer: '9',
      },
      {
        question: '45 / 9',
        choices: ['7', '4', '8', '5'],
        correctAnswer: '5',
      },
      {
        question: '25 / 5',
        choices: ['2', '5', '7', '9'],
        correctAnswer: '5',
      },
      {
        question: '36 / 4',
        choices: ['9', '2', '3', '6'],
        correctAnswer: '9',
      },
      {
        question: '42 / 6',
        choices: ['8', '7', '6', 'None of the above'],
        correctAnswer: '7',
      },
      {
        question: '48 / 8',
        choices: ['2', '7', '6', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '6',
      },
      {
        question: '24 / 4',
        choices: ['6', '8', '4', '5'],
        correctAnswer: '6',
      },
      {
        question: '15 / 3',
        choices: ['2', '3', '5', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '5',
      },
      {
        question: '64 / 8',
        choices: ['9', '3', '8', '7'],
        correctAnswer: '8',
      },
      {
          question: '81 / 9',
          choices: ['12', '2', '8', '9'],
          correctAnswer: '9',
        },
        {
          question: '30 / 6',
          choices: ['4', '3', '8', '5'],
          correctAnswer: '5',
        },
        {
          question: '56 / 8',
          choices: ['5', '3', '6', '7'],
          correctAnswer: '7',
        },
        {
          question: '40 / 5',
          choices: ['2', '3', '8', '6'],
          correctAnswer: '8',
        },
        {
          question: '48 / 8',
          choices: ['2', '4', '8', 'None of the above'],
          correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
        },
  ]
  export default questionL4